<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<AbnormalityCardsRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<Sephirah SephirahType="Keter">
		<AbnormalityCard ID="Bloodbath_Blood">
			<Abnormality>Bloodbath</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Blood</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
Take twice as much Stagger from attacks and deflects.
At the end of the Scene, recover from Stagger, gain 2 Strength and Endurance, and restore half of the character's Light if the character is Staggered.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>Unbearable depression overwhelms all who look into the bath.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">That person simply couldn’t take her sorrow in stride.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">Can you withstand this deep despair?</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">Come inside. Get into this dreadful pool of blood.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">Let go of it all, close your eyes, and sink into this bottomless pool.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">No matter how much blood is added, the bathtub never overflows.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="Bloodbath_Scar">
			<Abnormality>Bloodbath</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Scars</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
Take half as much Damage from attacks if the character is Staggered.
Once per Clash, heal HP equal to the attacker's natural dice roll upon being attacked.
Upon becoming Staggered, recover 25% of max HP.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>When I saw the latticework of scars on her severed wrist, I was reminded of our wine cabinet. That day, I popped the cork off the last one.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">It takes a strong will and courage to cut your own wrist.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">Don’t call these people foolish. You’re the biggest coward.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">The scars are marks of failure, but they aren’t worthless.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">Caress this pain filling the tub softly.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">The depth of a cut depends on the moment’s mind and willpower.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="Bloodbath_Hands">
			<Abnormality>Bloodbath</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Pale Hands</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
Speed Dice Slots +3. Two Speed Dice Slots become unavailable each Scene. At Emotion Levels II and V, one Speed Dice Slot becomes available.
When hit, inflict "Pale Hand" on the attacker.
(At the start of the Scene, inflict 1 Bind, Bleed, and Paralysis to self. At 3+ stack, also inflict 1 Disarm and Stagger Down. At 6+ stack, also inflict 1 Feeble and Damage Down.)
</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>Many hands float in the bath.
They are the hands of the people I once loved.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">The hands of one that you, perhaps we, loved are resting inside.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">These hands are waiting for someone to hold them, would you grant their wishes?</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">No matter how much you wish to grasp what slips through your fingers…</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">These hands earnestly want help, yet no one bothers to give them a glance.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">She must’ve trembled hard, the knife could slip from her hand at any moment.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="HeartofAspiration_Heart">
			<Abnormality>Heart of Aspiration</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Pulsation</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[All Allies]
Gain 1-2 Strength at the end of each Scene.
At the end of each Scene, if the librarian did not deal any damage with Offensive dice, they lose 25% of their Max HP. (Max. 30)</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>Excessive aspiration would bring about unwarranted frenzy.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">Overwhelming aspiration is what leads to wrongful frenzy.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">Why won’t you wish for anything when you’ve earned such power?</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">He who holds power should rightfully wield it.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">Yes, feel the rapid beating of your heart.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">It seems we have a common goal we’re desperately wishing for, so allow us to help.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="HeartofAspiration_Doki">
			<Abnormality>Heart of Aspiration</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Urging</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
Increase Max HP by 15%. (Current HP increases accordingly)
Gain 1-2 Speed.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>When borrowed, its rate of contraction will double, enhancing the borrower’s vigor and strength.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">Never stop wishing for it, until the beats give an answer.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">Don’t you want to see the end of this thrill that’s about to burst?</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">Give a meaning to all things we’ve wished for.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">Join me in this feverish pulsation.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">Your craving will make the beats faster.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="HeartofAspiration_Atk">
			<Abnormality>Heart of Aspiration</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Fervent Beats</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
The selected librarian dies at the end of the third Scene after which this page was chosen.
Gain 4 Strength, Endurance, Haste, and Protection each Scene until death. All Stagger damage resistances change to "Ineffective".</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>A heart without an owner; it still beats even after being removed from its body.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">Yes, feel the rapid beating of your heart.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">If you keep craving and do nothing to sate it, it’ll become too big and burst eventually.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">Join me in this feverish and quick pulsation.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">Even if it means I must burst someday, I want to see the end of it.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">The more you aspire, the faster the beats will get.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="Pinocchio_Learn">
			<Abnormality>Pinocchio</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Learning</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
Add a 'Learn' page to hand: ‘Cost 2 - [Start of Clash] Replace all dice with ones on the opponent's page.’
The page is also included in the deck at the start of subsequent Acts.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>All the child could do was ‘learn’ by observing others and mimicking their behavior. And that was the problem.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">I’m keen to learn as usual. Would you like to see me learn?</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">People taught me how to speak.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">I’m not a fast learner. I just mimic what I see.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">It’s not hard to mimic others. I don’t have to think.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">I’ve learned lots of things, but I never go anywhere.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="Pinocchio_Lie">
			<Abnormality>Pinocchio</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Lies</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
At the start of the Scene, randomize the Costs of all pages whose original Cost is less than 4.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>People lie all the time. Why is that a bad thing?</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">People love to say things the other way round.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">They said it wasn’t for themselves. They were lying for the good of everyone…</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">Lalala… I sing along to the song of lies all the people sing.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">I see the world upside down, as people have taught me.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">Everyone lies, why are you saying it’s a bad thing?</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="Pinocchio_Curious">
			<Abnormality>Pinocchio</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Curiosity</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
At the start of the Scene, shuffle all pages into the draw pile and draw 4 pages.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>I’m keen to learn as usual. Would you like to see me learn?</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">I still have lots of things I want to know. There’s lots to learn.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">If I see various things… Will I learn that much?</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">I’m curious about this… curious about that… Oh, and what’s this?</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">I’ve never seen that before… Where did it come from, and how?</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="TheSnowQueen_Sord">
			<Abnormality>The Snow Queen</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Sword of Frost</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
Upon winning a clash, inflict 1-3 Bind next Scene at a 50% chance.
Deal +2-5 Stagger damage against targets with Bind.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>A queen lives alone in the frosty winter forest.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">The edge of this blade is sharp and cold.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">Only the warmth of spring can melt away this sword.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">The straight blade knows exactly where to point itself to.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">One day, when it gets warm enough for snow to melt, this sword shall too thaw away.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">When this weapon impales your heart, you’ll become oblivious of yourself for a moment.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="TheSnowQueen_Chu">
			<Abnormality>The Snow Queen</Abnormality>
			<CardName>A Kiss</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
After winning 2 or more clashes with a single Combat Page, inflict Ice Splinter to the opponent.
At the end of each Scene, characters with 3 or more Ice Splinters become Immobilized for the next Scene.
      </AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>The Snow Queen’s kiss froze his heart, and he couldn’t feel the cold anymore.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">Only those who know of the scent of roses can bring an end to it all.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">You must have had a warm heart once.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">Forgetting the cold, forgetting the memories, and at last…</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">Could a frozen heart that’s become numb to the cold thaw out?</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">Only the fortitudinous shall be able to rescue the frozen.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="TheSnowQueen_Snow">
			<Abnormality>The Snow Queen</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Blizzard</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
All characters except the selected librarian become Immobilized for this Scene.
Next Scene, all enemies are inflicted with 6 Bind.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>Spring arrived with blossoming roses. Its warmth melted the Snow Queen’s palace. No one remembered her, sleeping underneath.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">No one will realize that I am slumbering in this place.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">When this snow melts, I will also be forgotten.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">Is my castle melting away, has the warm spring truly arrived…?</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">The roses’ full bloom signals to me that spring has come.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">That person must not have wished for any more of this cold.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="QuietKid_Hammer">
			<Abnormality>Silent Girl</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Hammer and Nail</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
Upon a successful Pierce attack, inflict 1 'Nail' to the target.
If a character with 'Nails' is hit by a Blunt attack, they take bonus damage equal to 5x the amount of Nails in them, then all stacks of Nails are removed.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>When she drives the nail with her hammer, the crack in the mind will grow too wide, and shatter completely.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">I wonder if there’s a crack in your mind that I could hammer a nail in?</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">When a nail drives into a fissure, it gets twice as wide.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">You should’ve been quick to deal with the baggage in your mind.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">There’s no repair for a mind that has been cracked.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="QuietKid_Eyeshine">
			<Abnormality>Silent Girl</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Leer</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
Deal and take twice as much physical damage.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>The girl remains silent. She would simply glare at the core of one’s inner side with her deep eyes.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">…</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">……</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">………</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">You’re trembling so much. What makes you so afraid?</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="QuietKid_Guilty">
			<Abnormality>Silent Girl</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Guilt</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
Reduce incoming Stagger damage by 1-3.
When hit, the attacker takes Stagger damage equal to the physical damage this character received.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>However, when she met a person carrying ‘guilt’ or ‘fear’, the girl revealed the nail and hammer she had been hiding behind her back.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">You’re still holding onto those painful memories… You poor fellow.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">Don’t shove the responsibility on others. The agony is yours to bear.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">You were just too busy running away, weren’t you?</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">Dear, you seem to be quite… unnerved, aren’t you?</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
	</Sephirah>
</AbnormalityCardsRoot>