<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<AbnormalityCardsRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<Sephirah SephirahType="Yesod">
		<AbnormalityCard ID="ForsakenMurderer_Tie">
			<Abnormality>Forsaken Murderer</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Chained Wrath</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
Blunt dice gain 1-3 Power. Speed is fixed at 1.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>He wears a straitjacket, but is as free as any man. No amount of chains and restraints is enough to prevent him from committing violence.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">Even if my body is tied… I’ll be as free as any man.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">Release me… Why do I have to be bound!</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">Don’t look at me with those eyes. You’re the most pitiful ones here…</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">You’re not going to keep me shackled with this!</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">I may be a mess now, but you’ll have to fear me all the same.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="ForsakenMurderer_Metal">
			<Abnormality>Forsaken Murderer</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Metallic Ringing</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
Upon a successful Blunt attack, inflict 1 Bind and Paralysis next Scene. (Excludes Mass Attacks)</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>“My head… turning into metal… folds in my brain, being flattened…”</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">My head is ringing. I can hear the sound of metal, clear and loud…</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">It feels as if my head is turning to cold steel.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">Is my head actually turning into metal?</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">When I bash my head onto a wall, it makes a refreshing sound.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">If my head turns into steel, all the wrinkles in my brain will be gone.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="ForsakenMurderer_Violence">
			<Abnormality>Forsaken Murderer</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Violence</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
Lower the minimum value of all dice by 1, and raise the maximum value by 3.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>“What’s really pitiful is people like you dying to the likes of me.”</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">Don’t think that you’ve won by chaining me…</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">………</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">Ends… Begins. Ends again, begins once more…</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">When I bash my head onto a wall, it makes a refreshing sound.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="LittleHelper_Rest">
			<Abnormality>All-Around Helper</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Recharge</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
If the librarian has maximum Light at the start of a Scene, gain 1-2 Haste, and deal +2-7 damage with attacks for that Scene.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>However, the limbs were equipped with sharp instruments instead of cleaning supplies.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">Beepboop… Beep… Out of battery…</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">Please… recharge… to a nearby socket…</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">Please shut down… The helper-bot will switch off soon…</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">Switching to charge mode. You cannot give orders in this mode.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="LittleHelper_Pattern">
			<Abnormality>All-Around Helper</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Repetitive Pattern-Recognition</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
After every three clash wins, restore 1 Light and gain 1-2 Haste next Scene.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>The day I was sent to a new home for the first time, I gave them the gift they wanted so earnestly.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">When I’m done cleaning, people would always praise me!</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">They’re giving me orders with a loud voice. That means I’m doing a good job.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">Beepboop~ Piii! Pattern data accumulated.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">People love to shout when they compliment me.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">The helper-bot has excellent learning capabilities.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="LittleHelper_Clean">
			<Abnormality>All-Around Helper</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Clean</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
Offensive dice gain Power against enemies with slower Speed (+1 Power per point of difference, up to 3).</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>It recognizes a bad mood as a sign that the surroundings are dirty, and promptly enters cleaning mode.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">The helper-bot can help you with any household chores!</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">What kind of task do you want me to do? I can help with anything.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">Contamination scan complete. Initiating cleaning protocol.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">Beebeebeep~ Beep. Contamination spotted! Proceeding with trash disposal protocol.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">I will help you with my wide selection of tools.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="SingingMachine_Music">
			<Abnormality>Singing Machine</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Music</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[All Characters]
All characters deal +4-8 damage with attacks this reception. They also suffer +4-8 Stagger damage upon taking a hit.
Whenever an ally defeats an enemy, they recover 15 HP and Stagger Resist.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>But nothing could compare to the music it makes when it eats a human.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">Nothing makes as fascinating music as a human can.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">Don’t you want to hear a beautiful song? You already know how.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">Don’t you worry. I’m sure that one wants to be a fine instrument, too.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">People all carry musical talent in them.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">Those who are fortitudinous, come to me. Join me.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="SingingMachine_Rhythm">
			<Abnormality>Singing Machine</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Rhythm</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
For the duration of the battle, gain 1 Rhythm at the start of each Scene. Whenever a character with Rhythm makes a successful attack, a random character gains 1 Rhythm at a 25% chance next Scene.
(Rhythm: Gain 1 Strength, take additional Stagger damage from hits, lasts 1 Scene)</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>It was creating a rhythm.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">Everyone wants to hear my song again.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">Various sounds join together to create music.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">They’re all volunteering to be instruments…</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">If everyone threw their bodies into me, it’ll certainly create an even sweeter melody.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">You won’t want to hear any other music anymore.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="SingingMachine_Atk">
			<Abnormality>Singing Machine</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Musical Addiction</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
Offensive dice gain 1-3 Power.
Defensive dice roll 1.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>After all, art is a devil’s gift, born from despair and suffering. Never stop performing until the body crumbles to dust.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">All other music is nothing more than noise to me…</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">Make me move… Light my path with the songs!</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">Hahaha… Ha… What will I do? What can I do? Haha…</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">Eternal happiness would be mine if this tune lasted forever…</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">Yes! This is it… Behold this powerful melody!</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="Butterfly_White">
			<Abnormality>The Funeral of the Dead Butterflies</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Eternal Rest</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
Deal +2-7 damage and +2-5 Stagger damage against the enemy with the lowest current HP.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>People believed that they would become beautiful beings with small wings when they died. It’s a silly story. Nonsensical too.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">An eternal rest… May you rest in peace.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">They believed that they would become beautiful beings with small wings when they died.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">I’ll help liberate you from tormenting yourselves.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">They must have returned home, having earned what they wanted and being full of hope.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">Death may seem fearsome, it doesn’t compare to the terror of reality. It’ll feel liberating, rather.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="Butterfly_Fly">
			<Abnormality>The Funeral of the Dead Butterflies</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Lament</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
Deal +2-4 damage against an enemy with a status ailment.
If the librarian has a status ailment at the start of the Scene, gain 1-2 Strength.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>They say the mourner with a huge luggage on his back had come to be a savior to all.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">For you poor souls who cannot stop grieving… I offer my condolences.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">Grief for the dead, and early lament for the living.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">Frivolous forms of sadness such as tears will only wet the wings.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">Not a sliver of impurity is allowed for the mind of those who mourn, for it must remain reverent and solemn.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">Not a single proper flower blooms to honor the butterflies.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="Butterfly_Casket">
			<Abnormality>The Funeral of the Dead Butterflies</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Coffin</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
On hit against an enemy whose HP is at 50% or lower, Seal one Speed die of the target (Twice per Scene, Excludes Mass Attacks).</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>He’s carrying a coffin. A large coffin to pay tribute to the employees who have nowhere else to go. It is still too small to comfort those innocent sacrifices.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">A single coffin to pay tribute to those who had nowhere to go, wandering with the memory of an empty faith…</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">Where does one go when they die?</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">The weight of the butterflies that died in vain would be too great to carry.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">That large coffin, simply too small to comfort those innocent sacrifices.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">The fragile wings will keep fluttering, waiting for the moment to fall asleep.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="Matan_Request">
			<Abnormality>Der Freischütz</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Request</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
When there is no 'Requested Target' present, the first enemy the selected librarian hits is marked as one. 
Deal +3-5 damage against the Requested Target.
When the selected librarian defeats the Requested Target, fully recover Stagger Resist, and resolve twice as many books.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>Just as the Devil said, the bullets will puncture anything you please. Forever.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">Some call him a righteous hunter, while others would call him a bloodstained gunman.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">The bullets always travel across a straight line, along the horizon.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">I simply follow my impulse, pointing my rifle as I like.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">The advancing bullet has no morals, no good or evil intent.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">Sometimes I helped those in need or fought evil.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="Matan_Seven">
			<Abnormality>Der Freischütz</Abnormality>
			<CardName>The Seventh Bullet</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
Deal +1-7 damage with Offensive dice.
When an Offensive die draws or loses in a clash, deal damage equal to the dice value to the opponent.
Every 7th Melee or Ranged page targets random characters, including allies.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>The Devil proposed a childish contract: The last bullet would puncture the head of his beloved. The moment he heard that, he sought and shot all the people he loved.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">The last bullet will puncture the head of your beloved.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">You’re right… This magical bullet can truly hit anyone just like you say.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">The bullets will puncture anything you please. Forever.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">No bullet will ever be the last.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
		<AbnormalityCard ID="Matan_Flame">
			<Abnormality>Der Freischütz</Abnormality>
			<CardName>Dark Flame</CardName>
			<AbilityDesc>[Single Ally]
For the duration of the reception, the 'Endured/Ineffective' resistances of all characters change to 'Weak/Fatal'.
Gain 1-2 Haste and 2-4 Strength each Scene.</AbilityDesc>
			<FlaborText>One day, the marksman realized the Devil no longer followed him. He pondered why, then realized that his soul had already fallen to Hell from the beginning.</FlaborText>
			<Dialogues>
				<Dialogue ID="1">Was it despair that he wished for?</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="2">My soul began to burn bit by bit, until it ultimately descended to Hell.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="3">When one feels there’s nothing left to aim for, their soul falls down to Hell.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="4">The despaired heart couldn’t go out in a passionate flame. It would only burn with a cold fire.</Dialogue>
				<Dialogue ID="5">The despair shall linger around you at all times.</Dialogue>
			</Dialogues>
		</AbnormalityCard>
	</Sephirah>
</AbnormalityCardsRoot>